Changing the world one prank at a time.
The Yes Men is a comedy, documentary film directed by Dan Ollman.
A comic, biting and revelatory documentary following a small group of prankster activists as they gain worldwide notoriety for
impersonating the World Trade Organization (WTO) on television and at business conferences around the world.
Himself, played by Mike Bonanno.
Himself, played by Andy Bichlbaum.
Himself, played by Michael Moore.
Himself, played by Patrick Lichty.
Himself, played by Sal Salamone.
Chicago Newreporter, played by Phil Bayly.
The Yes Men is a 2003 American documentary film about the
early culture jamming exploits of The Yes Men.
The film revolves around "The Yes Men" — two anti-globalization activists, under the aliases Andy Bichlbaum and Mike Bonanno — who impersonate spokespeople for the WTO and affiliated corporations in order to secretly lampoon and satirize
these organizations with elaborate ruses and fraudulent announcements of ridiculous corporate decisions, in front of live, unsuspecting audiences (usually comprising businesspeople, university student bodies, and the press).
The film details the two activists' involvement in
hoaxes targeting SimCopter, the 2000 G.
Bush presidential campaign, McDonald's, and, most prominently, the WTO.
The film also includes brief interviews with Michael Moore and Greg Palast.
The film premiered at the 28th Toronto International Film Festival in 2003.
It was also shown as part of a special screening at
the 2004 Sundance Film Festival.
The film received generally positive reviews from critics.
It is followed by a sequel, The Yes Men Fix the World.
The film explores themes of globalization, political activism, third
world, market economy, anti-globalisation activist.
The tone is lighthearted.